<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:gsx='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006/extended'><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>speakers</title><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ'/><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic'/><author><name>alsutton.com</name><email>alsutton.com@googlemail.com</email></author><openSearch:totalResults>27</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cokwr</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 2</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Al Sutton, speakercompany: Funky Android Ltd., speakerabstract: Al is Company Director of Funky Android Ltd who develop sites and software for the Google Android operating system. In the past he has worked on interactive TV systems from TwoWayTV and developing ticket bookings and email systems on Psion handhelds. Also he once worked for Chase Manhattan bank and Reuters in development infrastructure, DR facilities and security roles.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cokwr'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cpzh4</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 3</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Tom Mleko, speakercompany: HyperBees Ltd., speakerabstract: Tom is a co-founder of HyperBees Ltd, a company publishing apps for Android. He works with independent developers on enhancing their apps’ selling potential. Before HyperBees, Tom worked in a management consulting company and the global IT department of an FMCG multinational.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cpzh4'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cre1l</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 4</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Seb Lee Delisle, speakercompany: Plugin-In Media, speakerabstract: Seb loves all things beautifully digital and is the founding partner at award-winning agency Plug-in Media. He specialises in casual games, physics, motion detection, 3D and visual effects (like particle systems). His work has pushed the boundaries of what is possible both on and off the web, and has received many accolades including a BAFTA for the Plug-in Media project Big and Small for the BBC.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cre1l'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/chk2m</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 5</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Sean Owen, speakercompany: Independant, speakerabstract: Sean Owen co-developed Barcode Scanner for Android and the underlying "ZXing" scanning library with "20% time" at Google in 2007. It was subsequently open-sourced and helps power most barcode scanning Android and iPhone apps today, such as RedLaser. He works in technology investing in London and remains an active Android hobbyist.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/chk2m'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/ciyn3</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 6</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Iris Lapinski, speakercompany: Centre for Digital Inclusion, speakerabstract: Iris runs CDI Europe. She has a background in commercial digital media &amp; telecoms consulting working for Ovum and Farncombe Technology. During that time Iris managed a range of due diligence, business planning and strategy projects especially in Sub-Saharan Africa and the Middle East. Previously, Iris worked as a buy-side analyst for Dexia Asset Management in Belgium covering the telecoms, media and technology sectors.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/ciyn3'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/ckd7g</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 7</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Roman Nurik, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Roman is an Android Developer Advocate at Google, focusing on user experience, visual design, and multimedia. Previously, Roman worked on Google's geospatial developer products and engaged in web design and development work on a variety of independent projects.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/ckd7g'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/clrrx</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 8</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jan-Berkel, speakercompany: SoundCloud, speakerabstract: Jan Berkel is based in Berlin where he works as a software developer for the music sharing website SoundCloud. For a change he hacks on several open source Android projects, usually with the goal to make languages other than Java available on the platform. So far both Scala and Ruby look very promising.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/clrrx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cyevm</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 9</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Mark Murphy, speakercompany: Commonsware, speakerabstract: Mark Murphy is the founder of CommonsWare and the author of the Busy Coder’s Guide to Android Development and other books on Android application development. A three-time entrepreneur, his experience ranges from consulting on open source and collaborative development for the Fortune 500 to application development on just about anything smaller than a mainframe. He has been a software developer for over 25 years, from the TRS-80 to the latest crop of mobile devices. A polished speaker, Mr. Murphy has delivered conference presentations and training sessions on a wide array of topics internationally.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cyevm'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cztg3</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 10</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Tom Hume, speakercompany: Future Platforms , speakerabstract: Tom is MD of Future Platforms, a 10-year old software company that designs, develops and launches lovely software products for mobile phones, with an emphasis on collaboration, participation and playfulness. Their recent clients include Nokia, Microsoft, the BBC, and Hasbro.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cztg3'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d180g</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 11</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Antony Ribot, speakercompany: Ribot, speakerabstract: Antony is co-founder of ribot - a design lab specialising in enjoyable small screen interfaces and experiences.He is an ants and bees-inspired designer/developer/entrepreneur with a passion for making our mobile experiences usable, intuitive, fun and simple. Can be bribed with rustic French food.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d180g'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d2mkx</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 12</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Robin Spinks, speakercompany: RNIB, speakerabstract: Robin is the Principal Manager for Digital Accessibility at the Royal National Institute for the Blind in the UK.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d2mkx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cssly</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 13</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Aaron Miller, speakercompany: Couch.io, speakerabstract: Programmer from Arkansas, US, working at Couch.io after porting CouchDB to Android.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cssly'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cu76f</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 14</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Fee Beyer, speakercompany: Deutsche Telekom, speakerabstract: Fee is a Founder of Mobile Monday Berlin and member of the advisory Board for the MLOVE ConFestival. Working for Deutsche Telekom’s Product &amp; Innovation department, she scouts trends in the area of Personal Communication and develops concepts for mobile apps. In her previous career, she has worked for various mobile startups, helping them develop and execute their marketing strategies and product launches.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cu76f'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cvlqs</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 15</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jerome Ribot, speakercompany: Ribot, speakerabstract: Jerome is co-founder of ribot - a design lab specialising in enjoyable small screen interfaces and experiences. He heads up design and strategy for the company, and has created unique and simple experiences for 100s of millions of devices worldwide. Can be bribed with Gyokuro and minimal techno"</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cvlqs'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cx0b9</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 16</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Volker Hirsch, speakercompany: Scoreloop, speakerabstract: Volker is the Chief Strategy Officer at social infrastructure software specialists Scoreloop who bring sociality including monetization tools to mobile platforms and the web. He is also a co-founder of Blue Beck, a smartphone games studio.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/cx0b9'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d9ney</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 17</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Reto Meier, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Reto is a Developer Advocate for Android at Google and the author of 'Professional Android 2 Application Development'. He works closely with Android developers, helping them understand Android and how to bring rich, compelling apps to the Android Market. An experienced software developer with more than 10 years of experience, he has worked in various places and industries, including offshore oil and gas in Australia and finance in London.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d9ney'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/db1zf</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 18</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Nick Hunn, speakercompany: WiFore Consulting Ltd., speakerabstract: Nick Hunn advises on all aspect of wireless design and applications through his role in WiFore Consulting. He is actively involved in developing the Bluetooth standards, particularly in the area of Health, Smart Energy and M2M. He is a member of the Mobile Data Association, where he takes a special responsibility for promoting the development of eHealth to Government bodies, mobile networks and device manufacturers.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/db1zf'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dcgjs</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 19</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Greg Taylor, speakercompany: TigerSpike UK, speakerabstract: Greg is the Design &amp; UI/UX Director at TigerSpike UK. Day-to-day he embraces the opportunities and challenges faced within the mobile and social media landscapes. Holding a Masters in Graphic Design, he focuses on UI/UX, innovation, fast-evolving technology platforms, and the way in which users interact with devices, software, and each other. Greg’s fascinated by the future of technology and the way in which we’ll interact with it – or perhaps the way it will interact with us.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dcgjs'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/ddv49</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 20</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Russell Buckley, speakercompany: AdMob, speakerabstract: Russell champions the mobile channel for Google, communicating with publishers, developers and advertisers throughout the world. Previously, Russell was an early employee of AdMob, before it was acquired by Google in 2010. He has been in mobile marketing since 2000 and has subsequently been involved in thousands of campaigns. Before that he spent many years in marketing on both the agency and clientside. Russell is a previous Global Chairman of the Mobile Marketing Association, a founder of Mobile Monday in Germany and is a prolific writer about all things mobile., speakerldap: russellbuckley</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/ddv49'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d415a</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 21</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: David Bailey, speakercompany: Device Anywhere, speakerabstract: David has been with DeviceAnywhere for 2 years and has worked in mobile application testing for over 6 years, working with everyone from individual developers through to the largest handset vendors and operators. DeviceAnywhere provides convenient and cost-effective end-to-end solutions for mobile content development, testing, monitoring, certification, test automation and deployment – enabling application developers to bring better content to market faster than ever before. DeviceAnywhere products are accessible over three core technology platforms to address specific use cases of mobile application developers.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d415a'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d5fpr</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 22</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Limvirak Chea, speakercompany: InMobi, speakerabstract: Limvirak joined InMobi in May of 2010 and leads business development for Europe and the Middle East. Prior to InMobi, he spent four years at Google  where he lead  Strategic Partnerships focusing on mobile and distribution and then moved onto Google's New Business Development team helping the Product and Engineering teams bring new products to market through early-stage, exploratory deals and engaging with the tech community.  Limvirak has also led the Android Market in Europe and prior to Android, he worked on Open Social, Google's social API. Prior to Google, he defined and implemented the voice over IP strategy for AOL in Paris, and worked as a senior consultant in Telecom &amp; Media at Bossard Consultants; now Cap Gemini Consulting Services. Limvirak graduated from the Ecole Centrale Paris with a Diplôme d'Ingénieur, and holds a Masters in Electrical Engineering from Cornell University.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d5fpr'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d6ua4</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 23</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Marnix Dekker, speakercompany: ENISA, speakerabstract: Marnix works in the European Network and Information Security Agency's Secure applications program. He focuses on Smartphone security, Secure software engineering and Cloud security.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d6ua4'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d88ul</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 24</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Kieran Gutteridge, speakercompany: IntoHand, speakerabstract: Co-Founder of Intohand Ltd, a software company in Bath that develops tools, bespoke native applications and mobile web solutions for Android, iPhone and Java based small screen devices.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/d88ul'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dkvya</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 25</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Nick Hunn, speakercompany: WiFore Consulting Ltd., speakerabstract: Nick Hunn advises on all aspect of wireless design and applications through his role in WiFore Consulting. He is actively involved in developing the Bluetooth standards, particularly in the area of Health, Smart Energy and M2M. He is a member of the Mobile Data Association, where he takes a special responsibility for promoting the development of eHealth to Government bodies, mobile networks and device manufacturers.

Nick has over thirty years of experience in design and technical evangelisation, developing a diverse range of products, ranging from robot vision systems to laser gyroscopes, M2M communications systems and semiconductor processing equipment. He was also responsible for a world leading range of sperm and embryo freezers which won the Queen’s Award for Technology.
Over the last fifteen years, Nick has been heavily involved with wireless standards and has been intimately involved with the development of Bluetooth. He is now one of the key evangelists for the new low energy Bluetooth technology. He has been described as a “technology optimist”.

Within the Bluetooth standards group, Nick is Chair of the Bluetooth evangelisation committee and co-chair of the Medical Working Group. He is also the Bluetooth liaison officer for the Continua Health Alliance. He has been heavily involved in defining the new Bluetooth low power standard for web connected devices.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dkvya'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dmair</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 26</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Richard Hyndman, speakercompany: Mippin, speakerabstract: Richard Hyndman is the Chief Technology Officer and co-founder of Mippin. With over ten years of experience in the technology industry, most of which have been dedicated to mobile. Richard has a serious passion for Android. His company, Mippin, works with large-scale mobile operaters and handset manufacturers to deliver high quiality content-based applications to consumers worldwide.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dmair'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dnp34</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 27</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jim Small, speakercompany: Orange, speakerabstract: Jim Small is Head of Country Deployment and Operations for Application Shop within the Mobile Multimedia team in Orange Group Innovation Marketing with responsibility for delivery and operational running of Orange App Shop across all Orange France Telecom global markets. Jim and his team work directly with the Orange country product marketing heads to ensure local country requirements are delivered, and also manage direct relationships with the with application developer community to ensure that the sourcing and delivery of application content for Orange App Shop delivers to multi-country, multi-language and multi-platform requirements.

Jim joined Orange Group in March 2009 following 6 years in the Orange UK Multimedia team including project delivery responsibility for the initial Orange World portal and moving on to business ownership of the UK Multimedia Communication Services portfolio (Chat, IM, Email, Blog, Postcards), leadership of the UK downloads team and product portfolio (music tracks, ringtones, games, video &amp; TV and wallpapers) including UK business ownership for launch of the UK web and mobile Application Shop in 2007.

Prior to working at Orange Jim has a background in client service and project management within the New Media agency world and, before that, in the development of electronic publishing technologies for typesetting and pre-press.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dnp34'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dp3nl</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 28</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Martin Wrigley, speakercompany: Orange, speakerabstract: Martin Wrigley is Director of Developer Services for Orange France Telecom, working on the Orange Application Shop programme and the Orange developer programme; Orange Partner.
Orange Partner provides developers with the contacts, information, tools and support required to build and sell mobile applications and solutions to 150 million-plus Orange customers across the globe and is rolling out the Orange Application Shop across the 20+ Orange territories.

Martin has 25 years of experience in telecoms and IT, and joined Orange in 1992. Martin is also currently Chairman of Java Verified and Acting chair of the Unified Test Initiative.</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od7/public/basic/dp3nl'/></entry></feed>