<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:gsx='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006/extended'><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>sessions</title><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ'/><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic'/><author><name>alsutton.com</name><email>alsutton.com@googlemail.com</email></author><openSearch:totalResults>30</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/b8lvi</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 2</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:00pm, room: 1, sessiontitle: Android has a 'Dude' problem, track: Design, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Belinda Parmar, speakers: belindaparmar, sessionabstract: Lady Geek's research with YouGov has shown that women are much less likely to consider Android. For most women, the iPhone is still the preferred device despite the fact it is not the most technically capable smartphone on the market. If companies want to pierce the Apple bubble, they need to understand what women want. And that is not pink handsets with horoscopes and period tracker apps., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Android-has-a-dude-problem</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/b8lvi'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/c7q1z</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 3</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 1:30pm-1:45pm, room: 1, sessiontitle: Monetize your apps in emerging markets, track: Business, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Chua Zi Yong, speakers: chuaziyong, sessionabstract: How to Monetize Your Android Applications in Emerging Markets (China, India, Indonesia and others).

It is easy to spot that emerging markets such as China, India and Indonesia represent strong potential in market growth for smart phone applications. However, these are also extremely difficult markets to break into given the vast difference in user demographic and fragmentation. What are the challenges and issues for mobile developers will need to solve in order to game the market? This session will highlight some of the key issues that you need to know, and showcase MoVend, the in-app monetization solution for Android, sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Monetize-your-apps-in-emerging-markets</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/c7q1z'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/ba0fz</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 4</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 10:00am-10:30am, room: 2, sessiontitle: AIR 2.5 for Android, track: Design, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Seb Lee Delisle, speakers: sebleedelisle, sessionabstract: Seb will be talking about AIR 2.5 and using Flash on Android. Awaiting full talk details., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/AIR-2.5-for-Android</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/ba0fz'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bwhin</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 5</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 10:00am-10:30am, room: 1, sessiontitle: Driving Downloads via Intents, track: Developer, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Sean Owen, speakers: seanowen, sessionabstract: Using intents, Apps can be used like a library or API. This can be a powerful way to drive downloads for some applications., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Driving-Downloads-via-Intents</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bwhin'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bbf0c</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 6</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 10:35am-11:00am, room: 3, sessiontitle: JRuby on Android, track: Developer, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Jan-Berkel, speakers: janberkel, sessionabstract: JRuby on Android, sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/JRuby-on-Android</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bbf0c'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bctkt</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 7</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 10:35am-11:00am, room: 4, sessiontitle: The Glass Platform, track: SDK, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Friedger Muffke, speakers: friedgermuffke, sessionabstract: This presentation will introduce the SDK and the opportunities around the Android VOIP desktop phone in business offices. The device architecture as well as the software features are explained. Developers will learn how this SDK differs from the 'vanilla' SDK and what to think about when taking apps to the desktop phone., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/The-Glass-Platform</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bctkt'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cdcbn</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 8</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 10:35am-11:00am, room: 2, sessiontitle: Apps for Good. Innovation on the fringes of Android, track: Business, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Iris Lapinski, speakers: irislapinski, sessionabstract: Apps for Good. Innovation on the fringes of Android, sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Apps-for-Good.-Innovation-on-the-fringes-of-Android</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cdcbn'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bpgoi</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 9</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 10:35am-11:00am, room: 1, sessiontitle: Excellence in the Android User Experience, track: Design, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Roman Nurik, speakers: romannurik, sessionabstract: Excellence in the Android User Experience, sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Excellence-in-the-Android-User-Experience</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bpgoi'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bjueu</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 10</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:00pm, room: 1, sessiontitle: Best of UK mobile business 1, track: Business, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Tom Hume, Anthony Ribot, speakers: tomhume,anthonyribot, sessionabstract: Tom &amp; Antony will be kicking off this double session with presentations on lessons learned whilst winning business for mobile design and development., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Best-of-UK-mobile-business-1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bjueu'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bl8zb</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 11</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:00pm, room: 2, sessiontitle: Mobile UX for the Blind and partially sighted, track: Design, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Robin Spinks, speakers: robinspinks, sessionabstract: Rob Spinks of the RNIB will share some considerations and advice for all those wanting to develop accessible usable interfaces., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Mobile-UX-for-the-Blind-and-partially-sighted</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bl8zb'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bmnjo</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 12</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:00pm, room: 3, sessiontitle: Android Reuse Models, track: Developer, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Mark Murphy, speakers: markmurphy, sessionabstract: The development community needs to get into more of a reuse mindset, so that recommended patterns and snazzy UIs get reused, not rewritten., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Android-Reuse-Models</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bmnjo'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/ceqw0</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 13</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:00pm, room: 4, sessiontitle: Bridging the gap, track: SDK, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Patrick McGarry, speakers: patrickmcgarry, sessionabstract: This talk will present the historic difficulties in working with network operators and what is being done to change those interactions to a more open ecosystem.

A common ideal in product marketing and outreach is finding a way to build a thriving community around a branded product or solution. Unfortunately, most forays into this space ultimately fail (or meet with lackluster results) because of a fundamental lack of understanding about potential content creators -- especially developers -- by upper echelons of management. This talk will describe what is being done to bridge the gap between developer communities and the corporate world and how developers can help accelerate this process., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/bridging-the-gap</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/ceqw0'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bxw30</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 14</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 12:05pm-12:30pm, room: 1, sessiontitle: Android and CouchDB, track: Developer, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Aaron Miller, speakers: aaronmiller, sessionabstract: Why CouchDB is useful for mobile devices, it gives you synchronisation for free. Aaron will explore the current state of Android CouchDB., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Android-and-CouchDB</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bxw30'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bo245</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 15</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 12:05pm-12:30pm, room: 4, sessiontitle: Understanding smartphone traffic, track: SDK, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Per Willars, speakers: perwillars, sessionabstract: Until recently, the key optimization objectives for mobile broadband networks have been focused on throughput and peak data rates. The drastic uptake of smartphone usage has however created a traffic pattern with a high frequency of data activities, often with moderate data volumes. This traffic pattern is highly impacting the battery life of the device, and is in some cases also challenging the mobile broadband network with a high signaling load.

This talk will provide an understanding of the interaction between application traffic patterns and the 3G radio state machine, and also outline some advice for more radio-friendly application traffic patterns., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Understanding-smartphone-traffic</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bo245'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/caj6t</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 16</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 12:05pm-12:30pm, room: 1, sessiontitle: Best of UK mobile business 2, track: Business, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Kieran Gutteridge, Tom Hume, Richard Hyndman, Joe Neale, Antony Ribot, sessionabstract: Whilst cases of mobile developers striking gold with one application that becomes extremely popular do exist, they are rather rare. Serious mobile developers need to seek and win commissioned work to make ends meet, using this to fund the time spent working on interesting ideas for new apps. This panel seeks to explore a range of examples of the opportunities in Android development.

This session features the founders of successful UK mobile development companies talking candidly about the industry and how to succeed. They will be joined by Joe Neale, Founding Principle of M8 Capital, adding the view of a London based VC fund. In this panel, delegates will get to ask our experts for advice and ideas on real business situations that they have experienced or may have to negotiate in the future., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Best-of-UK-mobile-business-2</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/caj6t'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/c0p7u</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 17</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 12:05pm-12:30pm, room: 2, sessiontitle: How to develop an app concept, track: Design, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers:  Fee Beyer , speakers: feebeyer, sessionabstract: Fee will describe the frameworks she uses when creating app concepts from scratch., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/How-to-develop-an-app-concept</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/c0p7u'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/c6bhi</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 18</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:00pm, room: 2, sessiontitle: App Ltd – a business-like approach to your Android app, track: Business, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Tom Mleko, speakers: tommleko, sessionabstract: What do you need besides a brilliant idea and your excellent coding skills? A business-like approach could help., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/App-Ltd-a-business-like-approach-to-your-Android-app</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/c6bhi'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bzanh</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 19</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:00pm, room: 1, sessiontitle: Implementing Android: a manufacturer’s perspective, track: Design, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Erik Hellman, speakers: erikhellman, sessionabstract: In this session Erik Hellman will present how Sony Ericsson implements Android on phone, from the beginning of a project until it is released to customers. You will learn about intricate details of Android usually only concerning manufacturers and operators. We will look at the challenges that a manufacturer face with an open platform, the opportunities presented and the conflicts between requirements that you probably never would imagine. If you are interested in Android from a manufacturer perspective, you should definitively not miss this session., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Implementing-Android-a-manufacturers-perspective</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/bzanh'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cokwr</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 20</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:00pm, room: 3, sessiontitle: Turn good ideas in to great apps, track: Developer, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Reto Meier, speakers: retomeier, sessionabstract: Starting with an overview of the 5 deadly sins and 5 golden rules, you will learn how to build apps that users love and that are good citizens of the mobile environment., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Turn-good-ideas-in-to-great-apps</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cokwr'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cpzh4</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 21</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 2:30pm-3:00pm, room: 4, sessiontitle: Getting over the hurdles, track: SDK, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: David Bailey, speakers: davidbailey, sessionabstract: Android fragmentation still persists but developers face other challenges in getting their app to market. A lack of effective marketing channels, complicated and expensive submission and certification procedures, and inefficient planning and testing solutions aren’t helping. How can mobile operators and application store providers improve their relationships with application developers and shorten the development / testing/certification cycle?

David Bailey of DeviceAnywhere will share his first-hand knowledge of the current trends and issues facing mobile developers today. He will draw upon experiences from real customers to provide insight and expert commentary on the following issues:

· Addressing the key challenges application developers face in bringing their applications to the market

· Overcoming location, platforms and diversity of devices through remote mobile device testing across multiple devices and platforms

· Streamlining the development, testing and certification processes to attract more application developers

· Practical advice on speeding up the testing process and ensuring a positive user experience through test automation, usability and performance testing

· Improving the test certification process through a centralised and easy to manage certification system, sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Getting-over-the-hurdles</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cpzh4'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cre1l</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 22</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 3:05pm-3:30pm, room: 2, sessiontitle: Designing the mobile shopping experience of tomorrow, today, track: Design, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Jerome Ribot, speakers: jeromeribot, sessionabstract: This talk will take a look at the processes and thought required to design a mobile shopping experience. The Ribot design studio have recently released the Tesco mobile shopping app to wide spread acclaim., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Designing-the-mobile-shopping-experience-of-tomorrow-today</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cre1l'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cbxr6</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 23</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 3:05pm-3:30pm, room: 3, sessiontitle: Android beyond the phone; Tablets, eReaders, and more, track: Developer, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Al Sutton, speakers: alsutton, sessionabstract: This talk will introduce some of these new devices, explain some of the challenges that they can present to developers., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Android-beyond-the-phone-Tablets-eReaders-and-more</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cbxr6'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/chk2m</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 24</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 3:05pm-3:30pm, room: 1, sessiontitle: Making money on Android: The economics of apps, track: Business, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Volker Hirsch, speakers: volkerhirsch, sessionabstract: This talk will show how developers can adapt their games and apps to the changed environment of crowded app stores and demonstrate smart use of social tools., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Making-money-on-Android-The-economics-of-apps</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/chk2m'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/c94mc</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 25</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 3:05pm-3:30pm, room: 4, sessiontitle: The Real economics of mobile advertising, track: SDK, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Limvirak Chea, speakers: limvirakchea, sessionabstract: Advertising offers an excellent opportunity for developers to earn a living, but the industry has done little to educate on the real economics of the mobile advertising opportunity for developers. How many downloads do I need? What are the economics? How many impressions should I generate? Join InMobi's Limvirak Chea as he provides hard data and insight on what it takes to earn a living, what to expect across various countries and networks, and how we can learn from others who have been successful. InMobi will provide hard data on the economics, global research on the various ad platforms including Android and iPhone, and two case studies from both a B2B and B2C application.

Attendees will leave with an understanding of what to expect and what is required to build a profitable business on an advertising model. An understanding of the size and opportunity globally across the various app platforms including iPhone and Android and key learning based on actual case studies from successful developers; Simpaddico, interactive gaming app and Econtact Pro; a B2B small business app., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/The-real-economics-of-mobile-advertising</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/c94mc'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cg5gh</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 26</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 4:00pm-4:30pm, room: 2, sessiontitle: Maximising revenues from your Android app, track: Business, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Russell Buckley, speakers: russellbuckley, sessionabstract: This session will cover everything you need to know about monetising mobile, ranging from developing your mobile advertising strategy and how you get started, to monitoring and optimising your earnings on an ongoing basis., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Maximising-revenues-from-your-Android-app</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cg5gh'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/ciyn3</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 27</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 4:00pm-4:30pm, room: 3, sessiontitle: Interface design for Android tablets, track: Design, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Greg Taylor, speakers: gregtaylor, sessionabstract: Greg's designs are behind some highly publicised IPhone/IPad Apps. Instead of being constrained by the well intentioned conventions of Apple, Greg speaks about how we can take Android tablet interfaces further than yet imagined., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Interface-design-for-Android-tablets</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/ciyn3'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/ckd7g</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 28</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 4:00pm-4:30pm, room: 3, sessiontitle: Evolving past the fingertip, track: Developer, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Nick Hunn, speakers: nickhunn, sessionabstract: New wireless standards are about to produce a generation of connected devices that we wear, carry with us, or have around the home, which can talk directly to the handset and to an Android application., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Evolving-past-the-fingertip</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/ckd7g'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/clrrx</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 29</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 4:00pm-4:30pm, room: 4, sessiontitle: AllJoyn, a leading-edge peer-to-peer technology, track: SDK, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Matt Michael, speakers: mattmichael, sessionabstract: Create new and innovative user experiences using AllJoyn, a leading-edge peer-to-peer technology.

In this session, you will learn how to leverage proximity-based peer-to-peer networks to create new and innovative user experiences. A new iteration of peer-to-peer technology, AllJoyn was created specifically for wireless and aims to help drive innovation by enabling ad hoc connectivity among multiple devices without the need for an intermediary server. AllJoyn allows for a superior, user-friendly networked experience with simplified discovery, easy group formation, equipotent participation (all users can enter and exit the network at will) and low latency.

Because AllJoyn is device, platform and transport agnostic with support for multiple programming languages, it is the ideal technology for those looking to proliferate their application or service across the widest possible consumer base. The SDK is now available (at no cost), providing new tools and resources to help you pull ahead in the increasingly competitive landscape of mobile apps and services., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/AllJoyn-a-leading-edge-peer-to-peer-technology</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/clrrx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cyevm</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 30</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 4:35pm-5:00pm, room: 1, sessiontitle: What Consumers Want – Trends in Mobile Services &amp; Applications, track: Business, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Jeremy Copp, speakers: jeremycopp, sessionabstract: Using comScore mobile market intelligence data we will explore the mobile service and applications space in terms of the consumers, the brands they access and how they engage through their handsets. The session will identify the demographics of mobile media users and how the key drivers in the market are creating opportunities for advertisers, service providers, marketers and application developers., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/What-Consumers-Want</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cyevm'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cztg3</id><updated>2010-10-18T14:12:25.299Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 31</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Friday October 29, sessiontime: 4:35pm-5:00pm, room: 3, sessiontitle: Smart Risks, track: Developer, product: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessionspeakers: Marnix Dekker, speakers: marnixdekker, sessionabstract: Given the rapidly increasing importance of smartphones to EU citizens, businesses and governments, ENISA (the European Network and Information Security Agency) considers it important to assess their security implications. As a first step ENISA is preparing a paper with the main benefits and risks of smartphones from the perspective of network and information security. The paper also gives basic security recommendations for different user groups on how to mitigate the security risks of smartphone usage. The paper is the result of consultation with experts from across the various smartphone vendors, smartphone OS vendors, mobile operators, smartphone application developers, and organizations in the public and private sector. The report is due to be finalized by mid November. ENISA plans to follow up on this report in 2011 with further activities in this area. In this talk I will discuss our approach, present the main items in the paper, and how they were derived and discussed by the experts., sessionlink: http://www.droidcon.co.uk/Friday/Smart-Risks</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/tgSTAE3qZuYLPOuATLCEFhQ/od6/public/basic/cztg3'/></entry></feed>